(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{16:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},28:function(e,t,n){},29:function(e,t,n){},36:function(e,t,n){},41:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(1),i=n(0),o=n.n(i),a=n(10),c=n.n(a),s=(n(28),n.p,n(29),n(22)),l=n(18),u=n(43),d=n(44),h=n(46),m=n(45),y=n(47),f=n(9),p=(n(36),n.p+"static/media/star.dccf64d1.svg"),g=function(){var e=Object(f.c)((function(e){return e.data})),t=Object(i.useState)(null),n=Object(l.a)(t,2),o=n[0],a=n[1],c=Object(i.useState)(!1),g=Object(l.a)(c,2),j=g[0],w=g[1],b={easy:1,medium:2,hard:3},O=Object(f.b)();Object(i.useEffect)((function(){}),[]);for(var _=[],x=1;x<=b[e.questions[e.currentIndex].difficulty];x++)_.push(Object(r.jsx)("img",{src:p,style:{height:20,width:20},alt:"logo"}));var S=function(e){var t=e.question,n=e.index,i=e.total,c=(e.score,[].concat(Object(s.a)(t.incorrect_answers),[t.correct_answer]).sort((function(){return Math.random()-.5})));return Object(r.jsxs)(r.Fragment,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("h3",{style:{alignSelf:"end"},children:"Question ".concat(n+1," of ").concat(i)}),Object(r.jsx)("p",{style:{alignSelf:"end"},children:Object(r.jsx)("small",{children:decodeURIComponent(t.category)})}),Object(r.jsx)("div",{style:{alignSelf:"end"},children:_}),Object(r.jsx)("p",{children:decodeURIComponent(t.question)}),Object(r.jsx)(u.a,{children:c.map((function(e){return Object(r.jsx)(d.a,{md:6,xs:12,children:Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{disabled:null!=o,onClick:function(){!function(e){a(e==t.correct_answer?"Correct":"Incorrect"),O(function(e){return{type:"SET_QUESTION_SCORE",score:e}}(e==t.correct_answer?1:0))}(e)},variant:"light",style:{marginTop:15,width:250},children:decodeURIComponent(e)})})}))}),null!=o&&Object(r.jsxs)(r.Fragment,{children:[Object(r.jsx)("p",{children:o}),Object(r.jsx)(h.a,{onClick:function(){n+1==i?w(!0):(a(null),O(function(e){return{type:"SET_QUESTIONS_INDEX",index:e}}(n+1)))},variant:"light",style:{marginTop:15,width:150},children:n+1==i?"Check Score":"Next Questions"})]})]})},q=parseInt(e.questionScore/(e.currentIndex+1)*100),v=parseInt((e.currentIndex+1)/e.questions.length*100),I=parseInt(e.questionScore/e.questions.length*100),C=(e.currentIndex+1)/e.questions.length*100;return Object(r.jsxs)(m.a,{fluid:!0,style:{width:"80%"},children:[Object(r.jsx)(y.a,{variant:"success",now:C,style:{marginTop:20}}),Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"Question-content",children:j?Object(r.jsx)("h1",{children:"Score: ".concat(e.questionScore)}):Object(r.jsx)(S,{question:e.questions[e.currentIndex],score:e.questionScore,total:e.questions.length,index:e.currentIndex})}),Object(r.jsxs)("div",{style:{display:"flex",flexDirection:"row",justifyContent:"space-between"},children:[Object(r.jsx)("span",{children:"Score: ".concat(q,"%")}),Object(r.jsx)("span",{children:"Max Score: ".concat(v,"%")})]}),Object(r.jsxs)(y.a,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(y.a,{striped:!0,variant:"success",now:q},1),Object(r.jsx)(y.a,{striped:!0,variant:"warning",now:v},2),Object(r.jsx)(y.a,{variant:"danger",now:I},3)]})]})};var j=function(){return Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(r.jsx)("div",{className:"App-content",children:Object(r.jsx)(g,{})})})},w=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,48)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,i=t.getFCP,o=t.getLCP,a=t.getTTFB;n(e),r(e),i(e),o(e),a(e)}))},b=n(7),O=n(17),_=n(20),x=n(21),S=n.n(x),q=n(5),v=n(16),I={questions:v,currentIndex:0,questionScore:0},C=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:I,t=arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0;switch(t.type){case"SET_QUESTIONS":return Object(q.a)(Object(q.a)({},e),{},{questions:t.payload.data||v,currentIndex:t.payload.index||0});case"SET_QUESTIONS_INDEX":return Object(q.a)(Object(q.a)({},e),{},{currentIndex:t.index});case"SET_QUESTION_SCORE":return Object(q.a)(Object(q.a)({},e),{},{questionScore:e.questionScore+t.score});default:return e}},E={isLoading:!1},T=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:E,t=arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0;switch(t.type){case"UI_START_LOADING":return Object(q.a)(Object(q.a)({},e),{},{isLoading:!0});case"UI_STOP_LOADING":return Object(q.a)(Object(q.a)({},e),{},{isLoading:!1});default:return e}},F={key:"root",storage:S.a,whitelist:[]},A=Object(b.c)({data:C,ui:T}),H=function(e,t){return A(e,t)},W=(Object(O.a)(F,H),function(){var e=Object(b.d)(H,Object(b.a)(_.a));return{store:e,persistor:Object(O.b)(e)}}),N=(n(39),n(40),W().store),D=(W().persistor,function(){return Object(r.jsx)(f.a,{store:N,children:Object(r.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(r.jsx)(j,{})})})});c.a.render(Object(r.jsx)(D,{}),document.getElementById("root")),w()}},[[41,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.4a070ae5.chunk.js.map